<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Daily Micah</title>
    <link>https://git-bafshar.github.io/benpod</link>
    <description>Daily briefing on AI, product leadership, and Orlando news</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:image href="https://git-bafshar.github.io/benpod/micahpod-artwork.jpg"/>
    <itunes:author>Ben</itunes:author>
    <itunes:email>ben.afshar@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Ben</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>ben.afshar@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:category text="Technology"/>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Micah — 2026-02-27</title>
      <description>This episode explores a landmark ethical standoff as Anthropic’s CEO draws a hard line against military AI access, alongside a look at the &quot;hardcore&quot; efficiency shifts and strategic partnerships reshaping the tech industry. We also track the growing pains of autonomous vehicles in local neighborhoods, falling mortgage rates, and the evolving science of &quot;AI neuroscience&quot; that prioritizes logical reasoning over raw computing power. From high-stakes corporate decisions to the latest updates in aerospace and housing, this briefing covers the essential shifts shaping our technology and our communities.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:35:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://git-bafshar.github.io/benpod/micahpod/micahpod-2026-02-27-073559.mp3" length="4788096" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://git-bafshar.github.io/benpod/micahpod/micahpod-2026-02-27-073559.mp3</guid>
      <itunes:duration>299</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Micah — 2026-02-27</title>
      <description>Dive into the dawn of the “agentic era” as AI moves from answering questions to executing complex tasks, sparking high-stakes ethical standoffs between tech giants and the military. This episode also explores the real-world friction of driverless cars in residential neighborhoods, the latest shifts in the housing market, and surprising developments in national security and global diplomacy.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:20:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://git-bafshar.github.io/benpod/micahpod/micahpod-2026-02-27-002045.mp3" length="4984704" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://git-bafshar.github.io/benpod/micahpod/micahpod-2026-02-27-002045.mp3</guid>
      <itunes:duration>312</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>